Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Computer Research in Music and Acoustics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
Cataloguesl Advertising 20
Catgut Acoustical Society 1991-1994 10
CCRMA Associatesl Affiliates 10
CCRMA Collaborative research 14
CCRMA Correspondence 13
CCRMA Histories and Timeline 13
CCRMA Overviews 1977-1994 13
CCRMA Search for Record (CD) Producer 1980s 6
CCRMA/France (historical) 10
CCRMA/ltaly 10
Cerebral Asymmetry Lusted 20
CNMA T/CCRMA Berkeley 10
CognitionlMemory 20
Computer Music Associations, Historical 13
Computer Music Groups, Late 1980s and 1990 13
Computer Music Research-International 14
Computer Music Research-National 14
Computer Music studios, 1960s 13
Computer Music Studios, Centers, 1990s 13
Computer Music 20
Computer Music, Acoustics Articles arranged alphabetically by author name 15
Computer SoftwarelHardware 20
DARPA 1985- Pierce and Jos proposal 2
DARPA-Mont-Reynaud, 1990 2
Digital Synthesis 20
Distance 20
Don, etc. 20
Donations-Private 5
Dowling 20
Early Summer Workshops 13
Ears Manual (I know it's absurd!) 20
Echo/Reverb/Prec. 20
Equipment- major 5
Equipment-minor 5
Funding History 1970s, 1980s 5
Funding Letters 1979-1980 Separation from AI and CS 5
Fundraising 1970s 5
Gen: (Y)ac & Music 20
Gestalt 20
Getty Symposium 1992 flyers, programs 10
Getty Symposium 1992 miscellaneous documents 10
Grammar 20
Historic Papers 1960s, 1970s, Mathews and Others 15
Historical Artifacts 13
Historical CD 6
Historical Memos-Facility Expenses and Receipts 13
History of Computer Music and Risset's Introductory Sound Catalogue 15
History of Computer Music-paper 1989-1991 14
IDEAMA miscellaneous docs. 6
Intelligent Systems for Musical Analysis 4
Intelligent Systems NSF Joint SCI/CCRMA 1980 proposal 4
International Historic Papers 14
Intervals 20
IRCAM news 10
IRCAM/Boulez, misc. 10
J. Chowning- Interviews 7
J. Chowning- Misc. letters 7
JAM 20
JASA 1 Reviewers 20
JASA 2/3 MDS Studies 1976 20
John Chowning miscellaneous paraphernalia 7
John Chowning personal file (press clips, review) 7
John Chowning programs, press clippings, concert reviews 7
Knoll Misc. Problems 1990s 5
Knoll Misc. Projects 5
Knoll Post-Quake Retrofitting 5
Knoll Problems 1980s 5
Knoll Refurbishing 5
LANCINO "Aloni" permissions 6
Lateralization 20
Ligeti, Gyorgy 10
Lists of Compositions Realized at CCRMA 13
Lists of Publications (Research Papers) and Sales 13
Matthews 20
Max Mathews Historical Papers 15
Max Matthews Research Proposals NSFINSA 1987 4
Mellon/IDEAMA funding 6
Membranophones 20
Misc. Hardware and Software 5
Miscellaneous Computer Music Events and Activities 10
Miscellaneous Funding Proposals 5
Miscellaneous Recording Projects 6
Miscellaneous 20
Move to Knoll 5
Move to Knoll-Memos, etc. 5
Music V Manual 15
Musical Cognition 21
Musical Performance 21
Naval Research -London 21
NEA Center for New Music Resources 1989 proposal and budgets 1
NEA Centers for New Music Resource 1985-1988 1
NEA-Centers Grants 1983-1984, 1984-1985 1
NEA Equipment Ifacility support 199-1983 1
NEA Equipment Grants 1986-1987, 1987-1988 1
NEA Facility Renovation Grant 1984-1987 1
NEA-McNabb "Robot Ballet" 1986 1
NEA-McNabb opera 1990 1
NEA Recording CCRMA composers 1981-1987 1
NEA Recordings 1987-1988 Chowning 1
NEA Sponsor/CCRMA recordings to Library of Congress 1994 1
NEA Synthesizer Maintenance Grant 1988-1989 1
NEA Wynton Marsalis Project 1
NEA-IDEAMA 1992-1994 6
NEH IDEAMA Grant 1993-1994 (Mathews) 6
NSF 1979 and 1980 Auditory Distance 4
NSF 1982-1984 "Intelligent Systems" 4
NSF 1985 4
NSF-1987 Pierce and Schubert 4
NSF 1993-1996 4
NSF and NEA Grant Letters 1975-1976 3
NSF Architecture-not funded-11 /20/ 1979 3
NSF -Chowning/Smith 1974-1975 "Perceptual Modeling" proposal and budget 3
NSF Chowning/Smith Grant 1976-1978 "Timbre Perception for Complex Time-Variant Tones" 3
NSF Grant 19975 News Articles 3
NSF Interactive Graphical Environments 1977-1979 Grant Approval 3
NSF Proposals (letters) 1987-1988 4
NSF Proposals 1988-1989 4
NSF Sound Localization 1112011 979 3
NSF Summary of Awards 1981 4
NSF/JOS 1996-2000 "Discrete-Time Simulation" 4
NSF-"Auditory Distance" 2 proposals-1979-198 1 4
NSF-"Timbre" research proposals, budgets, letters, 1977-1980 3
NSF-1977 Chowning, Grey, Moore, Moorer and Rush 3
NSF-John Chowning An Interactive Graphical Environment, Etc. 3
NSF-JOS-1994 Reject "Vocal Modeling" 4
NSF-L. Smith, 1. Chowning, Computer Simulation of Musical Instrument Tones, 1975 3
Old Photos scanned at CCRMA 13
Patents, licenses, agreements 7
People at CCRMA miscellaneous info, memos 13
Perception -general 21
Perception 21
Pitch 21
Presentations-TalkslDemos 10
Private donors 5
Psychoacoustics and Music Psychology 14
Psychology -Acoustics 21
Publish & Perish 20
Rockefeller proposals, grant 1980s 2
Rockefellerl Argentina Exchange 1990s 2
SDF-1982-1984 COMITS 2
SDF Annual Reports 1982-88 2
SDF Benchmark Symposium and Book on Computer Music 1985-1988 2
SDF CD Project 1988 2
SDF grants 1982 2
Shepard 21
Speech Perc. 21
Speech Research and Instrumentation 21
Stanford-Computer Science Reports 1965 1981 7
Stanford Programs Support CCRMA / Music 7
Stanford Support OTL etc 7
Studios-1970s, 1980s 13
Summaries ofNEA grants 1
Summer Workshop 1982 13
Summer Workshop 1983 13
Summer Workshop Files 1986-1990 13
Summer Workshop Materials 1984 13
Theremin, Leon 10
Timbre Perception 3
USEMUS November 1977 Manual 13
Various figures 20
Visitors 10
WERGO CD project 6
WERGO CD Series letters, Agreements 6
WERGO CD Series memo's, agreements, letters, content of series 6
WERGO CD Series Selected and Rejected Pieces-Letters 6
WERGO Selection letters 6
Yamaha 7
Yamaha-1988 proposal for endowment and computer lab 7
Yamaha-Original documents 7
ZKM Equipment docs 1991-1993 6